Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/bianca-myers-98018649 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Integrated Marketing
Digital Strategy
Digital Marketing

Honors-Awards

Cannes Lions Young Marketers Shortlisted for the 2014 NRA Marketing Award in North America

Bianca Myers

Managing Director

Toronto, Ontario, Canada

Summary

Experienced Team Lead with a demonstrated history of working in the marketing and advertising industry. Skilled in Digital Strategy, Customer Insight, Advertising, Integrated Marketing, and Digital Marketing. Strong sales professional with a Post Graduate Diploma focused in Creative Advertising from Seneca at York.

Experience

SALT XC

Managing Director January 2024 - Present (1 year 2 months)

Toronto, Ontario, Canada

123w (One Twenty Three West)
VP Managing Director
June 2022 - January 2024 (1 year 8 months)
Toronto, Ontario, Canada

The Kitchen Managing Director November 2021 - June 2022 (8 months)

Toronto, Ontario, Canada

lg2 Group Director July 2019 - October 2021 (2 years 4 months)

john st. 5 years 3 months

Team Lead
February 2019 - June 2019 (5 months)
Toronto, Ontario, Canada

Account Director

April 2014 - January 2019 (4 years 10 months) Toronto

Boston Pizza International Inc Marketing Manager April 2012 - April 2014 (2 years 1 month)

BBDO

Account Supervisor
June 2011 - March 2012 (10 months)
BBDO

Cossette

Account Supervisor
June 2007 - June 2011 (4 years 1 month)
502 King Street West

Education

Seneca at York

Post Graduate Diploma, Creative Advertising · (2005 - 2007)

University of Toronto

Bachelor's degree, Semiotics · (2001 - 2005)